Finding Aid for James Patrick Adams Papers, 1978-1981
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
James Patrick Adams Papers 1978-1981
Adams, James Patrick.
1 linear ft.
861054 Aa 2
Student at the University of Michigan, chairman of the University Activities Center, and special projects coordinator for the Michigan Student Assembly. Topical files relating to student life, his involvement in the activities and administration of West Quadrangle, and his participation in Ann Arbor politics.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The collection was donated in 1981 by James P. Adams (donor no. 6596 ).
The collection is open to research.
James Patrick Adams, II, was a student at the University of Michigan, chairman of the University Activities Center, and special projects coordinator for the Michigan Student Assembly.
The papers include topical files relating to student life, Adams' involvement in the activities and administration of West Quadrangle, and his participation in Ann Arbor politics.
Subjects:
Ann Arbor (Mich.)--Politics and government.; Michigan Student Assembly.; University of Michigan--Students--Social life and customs--1971-1980.
- Topical files
  - Ann Arbor Democratic Party (Box 1)
  - Fishbowl Renovation (Box 1)
  - Food Service Consolidation (Box 1)
  - Legislative Relations Committee (Box 1)
  - LSA-Student Government (Agendas and Minutes) (Box 1)
  - Michigan Daily Clippings
    - Michigan Student Assembly (Box 1)
    - Open Meetings Policy (Box 1)
  - Michigan Student Assembly (Minutes, 1979-1980 incomplete) (Box 1)
  - Michigan Union (Box 1)
  - National "On Campus" Reports, September 1979-August, 1980 (Box 1)
  - Quadrium Project (High Rise Apartment) (Box 1)
  - Special Projects, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Student Achievement Awards (Box 1)
  - Student Development Committee (Box 1)
  - Student Legal Service By-Laws (Box 1)
  - Students for Students (Box 1)
  - Undergraduate Political Science Association (Box 1)
  - University Activities Center
    - Interviews (Box 1)
    - Rally and Torch March, 1979 (Box 1)
    - Rally, 1980 (Box 1)
    - Staff Meetings (Box 1)
  - University of Michigan Republican Club (Box 1)
  - West Quad (Director's Letters) (Leon West Letters) (Box 1)
  - WQBN
    - General (Box 1)
    - Council and Programming, 1978-1979 (Box 1)
- Other papers
  - Correspondence (scattered) (Box 1)
  - Date books, 1978-1981, 3 volumes (Box 1)
  - Notebook re. Board for Student Publications, 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - Print-out of survey of readership of Michigan Daily. (Box 1)